// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Name the process where neural connection formation rate slows down to make the circuits more efficient?",
        answer: "Pruning",
        options: [
            "Depreviation",
            "Puring",
            "Pruning",
            "Decicuiting",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "select the correct capacities which are inextricably intertwined throughout the life course and are shaped by thr basic interaction of genes and experience of a developing brain?",
        answer: [
            "Cognitive",
            "Emotional",
            "Social",
        ],
        options: [
            "Cognitive",
            "Emotional ",
            "Physical",
            "Social",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Arrange in the Correct order the process of neural connections:",
        answer: [
            "The early age is the most active period",
            "1 million neuron connections are made every second",
            "Rapid proliferation occurs",
            "Pruning takes place",
        ],
        options: [
            "Pruning takes place",
            "1 million neuron connections are made every second",
            "Pruning takes place",
            "Decicuiting",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What reinforces the newly formed brain circuits?",
        answer: "Repeated ",
        options: [
            "Extensive Pressure",
            "Experience Repetitions",
            "Repeated use",
            "Automatic Reinforcement",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Young Children naturally reach out for interactions through?",
        answer: [
            "Babbling",
            "Gestures",
            "Expressions",
        ],
        options: [
            "Babbling",
            "Cellphones",
            "Gestures",
            "Expressions",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Arrange the steps to practice serve and return orderwise",
        answer: [
            "Notice the serve and share the focus of attention",
            "Return the serve by supporting and encouraging",
            "Give it a name",
            "Take turns and wait to keep the interaction going ",
        ],
        options: [
            "Give it a name",
            "Take turns and wait to keep the interaction going",
            "Notice the serve and share the focus of attention",
            "Return the serve by supporting and encouraging",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Result of long lasting  and extreme stress on a childs brain with no buffering relationships?",
        answer: "Damaged or weakend brain architecture",
        options: [
            "Emotionless Attitude",
            "Damaged or weakend brain architecture",
            "Mental In capabilities",
            "Stronger Personality",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Result of long lasting  and extreme stress on a childs brain with no buffering relationships?",
        answer: [
            "Cognitive",
            "Emotional",
            "Social",
        ],
        options: [
            "Emotionless Attitude",
            "Damaged or weakend brain architecture",
            "Mental In capabilities",
            "Stronger Personality",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What happens to the person who faces serious early adversities or such types of early age hardships for an prolonged ammount of time?",
        answer: [
            "Percive and focus mostly on negetives  such as life threats",
            "Lower Self Efficacy",
            "Lack of goal oriented behaviour",
            "Resulting in an overall slow development",
        ],
        options: [
            "Lack of goal oriented behaviour",
            "Resulting in an overall slow development",
            "Percive and focus mostly on negetives  such as life threats",
            "Lower Self Efficacy",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "How can children who suffer severe depreviation recover?",
        answer: "Theraputic intervention and highly supportive care",
        options: [
            "Theraputic intervention and highly supportive care",
            "Change of Living Environment to a Pleasant one ",
            "Living Alone away from previous enviorment",
            "Socialize",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Consequences of severe depreviation?",
        answer: [
            "Couognitive delays ",
            "Coutunning of physical growth",
            "Couisruption of body's stress response",
        ],
        options: [
            "Disrupts the child's way of thinking",
            "Alters the development of biological stress response system ",
            "Singnificant risk of emotional or interpersonal difficulties",
            "physical incapabilities",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What happens to the person who faces serious early adversities or such types of early age hardships for an prolonged ammount of time?",
        answer: [
            "Percive and focus mostly on negetives  such as life threats",
            "Lower Self Efficacy",
            "Lack of goal oriented behaviour",
            "Resulting in an overall slow development",
        ],
        options: [
            "Lack of goal oriented behaviour",
            "Resulting in an overall slow development",
            "Percive and focus mostly on negetives  such as life threats",
            "Lower Self Efficacy",
        ]
    },
];